在fragment_detail布局中，已经定义了一个TextView
In the fragment detailed layout, a text view
我们必须给它指定一个id
is already defined. We have to assign it an
这样的话在DetailActivity的DetailFragment中
ID so that within the detail fragment of detail
我们就能够用findViewById()
activity we can use findViewById to
来找到这个TextView。为了取得这个TextView
find the TextView. To determine the forecast
所要展示的天气预报信息
info that the text view should display. We can
我们可以在启动DetailActivity的Intent中找到它
access the intent that the DetailActivity was launched
我们准备在onCreateView()里这么做
by. We're going to use this inside of onCreateView.
因为我们已经向Intent的Extra添加了天气预报信息
[SOUND] Since we added an intent extra with the forecast
所以我们可以从Intent的Extra中读取出来，把它显示出来
data there. We can read that intent extra back to display in the text
如你所见，我们将预报信息从Intent中拉出来
view, as you can see we pulled the forecast string from the
找到rootView，然后将TextView的文字设置为预报信息
intent find our rootView and then set the text to that forecast string